//問題文を格納する要素です
const quiz = [
    {
      question: "Candidates who applied for the editor position were _____ to submit a portfolio and at least three references along with their resume.",
      answers: ["decided", "deserted", "expected", "exceeded"],
      correct: "expected"
    },
    {
      question: "Pomona Markets _____ customers that all of its products are competitively priced.",
      answers: ["requires", "inquires", "assures", "endures"],
      correct: "assures"
    },
    {
      question: "Jim Cornell received an excellent evaluation from his manager because he was _____ to raising funds.",
      answers: ["committed", "authorized" ,"commended", "declared"],
      correct: "committed"
    },
    {
      question: "Electra-Mart will _____ respondents to the questionnaire a twenty-five dollar voucher redeemable at its stores.",
      answers: ["offer", "concentrate", "waive", "train"],
      correct: "offer"
    },
    {
      question: "Cangrella Foods is making every possible effort to _____ the cause of the problem affecting its production line equipment.",
      answers: ["designate", "facilitate", "identify", "adjust"],
      correct: "identify"
    },
    {
      question: "Mr.Bovee's suggestion to _____ Ms.Brown to next month's company retreat was dismissed.",
      answers: ["include", "propose", "promote", "invite"],
      correct: "invite"
    },
    {
      question: "Apticom _____ an apology to patrons whose confidential information had been leaked and promised to strengthen its security.",
      answers: ["hailed", "extended", "replied", "appointed"],
      correct: "extended"
    },
    {
      question: "The directors are all _____ attending the charity gala at the Saville Hotel in Paris.",
      answers: ["looking forward to", "bringing about", "living up to", "picking up"],
      correct: "looking forward to"
    },
    {
      question: "Globrex Industrial's annual shareholders' meeting _____ with a speech from Hayato Matsui, the company's chief executive.",
      answers: ["negotiated", "accumulated", "enclosed", "concluded"],
      correct: "concluded"
    },
    {
      question: "Staff members have to _____ receipts from business trips to the human resources department to be reimbursed for travel costs.",
      answers: ["result", "consult", "provide", "divide"],
      correct: "provide"
    },
    {
      question: "The delegation members who _____ the facility were impressed by how welding robots were being used.",
      answers: ["estimated", "toured", "emerged", "attached"],
      correct: "toured"
    },
    {
      question: "The complimentary shuttle service between the Arcewell Hotel and Hetwick Aquarium _____ on a summer schedule from July 1.",
      answers: ["operates", "endorses", "issues", "processes"],
      correct: "operates"
    },
    {
      question: "The way that nurses _____ out their duties varies according to the hospital department in which they work.",
      answers: ["take", "hand", "carry", "turn"],
      correct: "carry"
    },
    {
      question: "The store managers of FCG Electronics stores have the authority to _____ the retail selling prices of all items.",
      answers: ["acquire", "revise", "load", "account"],
      correct: "revise"
    },
    {
      question: "In order to _____ your subscription, you will need to complete and return the enclosed form.",
      answers: ["nominate", "renew", "speculate", "contend"],
      correct: "renew"
    },
    {
      question: "The training session will _____ many guest commentators who specialize in marketing analysis.",
      answers: ["launch", "posopone", "feature", "organize"],
      correct: "feature"
    },
    {
      question: "Go-Stream will be _____ the Sci-Fi Awards, so people can watch the event live on their computer or mobile device.",
      answers: ["regulating", "collaborating", "drafting", "covering"],
      correct: "covering"
    },
    {
      question: "The secretaries spent a considerable amount of time _____ the risk management workshops for each division.",
      answers: ["scheduling", "hesitating", "allowing", "struggling"],
      correct: "scheduling"
    }
  ];

